Jesse Stone: No Remorse is a drama, thriller,
crime film directed by Robert Harmon.
Police Chief Jesse Stone, who was suspended by the Paradise, Mass.
Town Council, begins moonlighting for his friend, State Homicide Commander Healy, by investigating a series of
murders in Boston, leaving Rose and Suitcase to handle a crime spree in Paradise on their own.
Jesse pours his energy into his work in an effort to push
away his twin demons: booze and women.
When his investigation leads to notorious mob boss Gino
Fish, Jesse's pursuit becomes hazardous.
Jesse Stone, played by Tom Selleck.
Rose Gammon, played by Kathy Baker.
Luther 'Suitcase' Simpson, played by Kohl Sudduth.
Commander Healy, played by Stephen McHattie.
Cissy, played by Krista Allen.
Gino Fish, played by William Sadler.
Jesse Stone: No Remorse is a 2010 American made-for-television crime drama film directed
by Robert Harmon and starring Tom Selleck, Kathy Baker, and Kohl Sudduth.
Written by Tom Selleck and Michael Brandman, it is based on
the Jesse Stone novels written by Robert B.
This film is about the police chief of a small New England town who investigates a series of murders in
Boston for a state police colleague and uncovers evidence that leads to a notorious mob boss.
Filmed on location in Nova Scotia, the story is set in the
fictitious town of Paradise, Massachusetts.
Jesse Stone: No Remorse is the sixth in a series of nine
television films adapted from Parker's Jesse Stone novels.
With David Gribble as cinematographer, the film was nominated for an American Society of
Cinematographers Award for Achievement in Cinematography, Motion Picture/Miniseries Television.
The film first aired on the CBS television network on May 9, 2010.
The tone is mind_bending and emotional and intense.